Heat. [music]
[music] Heat.
[music]
>> [music]
>> One, two, one, two, three.
>> Bounce what I got. Bounce what I got.
And I'm bouncing. Bounce what I got.
Lotto and my favorite white girl. Y'all
chewed this song up. It brought me back.
Bounce what I got. Bounce what I got.
And I got it. Verse eight. DOA. You ate
that DOA. What is going on you all?
Happy um Tuesday. I think today is
Tuesday. Hey big ones, little ones, and
the ones in between. Bounce what I got.
Bounce what I got. And I'm bouncing. Can
y'all hear me? Papa, can you hear me?
Um, the music video for Lotto and
Doaat's song. Okay.
Okay.
The song is cute.
Lotto, I don't know why you had that man
on that song. See, you having that 21
Savage man on there with that terrible
voice, that terrible verse.
It just made me not want to listen to
the rest of the album. But this brought
me back. DOA look good. Lotto look good.
lot. I don't care what the girls say.
They can call you scratch off, but girl,
it's giving some of the I want to
scratch and sniff. Okay, you was looking
good. Bounce what I got. The only issue
that I had with that music video is
the only I only had one issue with that
music video.
Only one issue. And I want y'all to tell
me what y'all issue was. Um, but my
issue was
girl
Why y'all got all these dark-kinned men?
Like,
what was what was that giving? I don't
know. I don't like when they do the
light-skinned person is the center and
the dark everybody else is dark skin. I
don't like I hate when they do that in
photo shoots. I hate when they do it and
I just I don't know. I was that made me
a little uncomfortable.
I don't know how to feel about that. You
just you could have just had like u
several different colors like you know
dark-kinned men, light-skinned men,
brownkinned men, all of the things.
Brown skin boy. But that dark the
darkkinned man like and you being the
center girl, it was reminding me of
um Game of Thrones when they was
uplifting um me.
It's just
I just wasn't feeling that. But we know
y'all like Well, we know Lotto like dark
skin me and child. We don't know about
my girl DOA. She love her white man
child. She love her concisador.
She love her colonizer. Bounce what I
got. She be rapping like she don't be
white man. [laughter]
They do got white mama. So it makes
sense. Come on Audrey. [laughter]
They do got some white mama. So yeah, I
I did find it was it was dehumanizing. I
I don't like when they do that. I don't
like when they do that. I don't like it.
But bounce what I got. Um, but we gotta
speaking of colorism, we got some things
to get into because Serena
Serena Williams, sister, I hate it for
you. We got to we got to we got to talk.
Serena Williams, you was on the docket
this week. You was on the docket for the
King of Reese's video this Tuesday
because the girls had did a side by side
picture of you. You know,
congratulations. You love where you at.
You you you wiggling your kneecaps
around a little bit, but sister, you got
on this Fedra Parks wig from um season
17, The Real Housewives of Atlanta, and
you got on somebody else skin. Girl, I
don't know what's going on. Girl, you
was dark skinned at one point. All the
girls were dark skin at one point. Now
y'all giving Paint What I got. This is
why Fenty Beauty is going out of
business cuz y'all not buying the right
shades no more. Y'all is over here
bleaching. Y'all bleaching queen. our
bleaching queen. [laughter]
You know what, Kevin? I wish I could put
this up, but YouTube already um got me
for our hot and spicy um live stream
that we did for the patrons. Strictly
for the patrons. We was on there being
hot and spicy. The girl said they had to
pull out their rose. A rose. It's still
a rose. Baby girl, it's going to send me
higher.
Artha was they can take you and make
you. Artha was singing child. Period.
They g metha
take you and break you. A rose is still
a rose. HEY WHAT I AM. Lauren Hill was
on there singing what I am. And girl
y'all gave me life. Y'all gave me life.
But yeah girl. Uh I don't know what that
music video was giving but bounce what I
got. Uh but Serena Williams
where my video uh
a bleaching girl's a bleaching girl. A
bleaching queen. A bleaching queen. The
girls is doing some new age bleaching.
They doing the bleaching where they can
I heard they can just put it in your
arm. They can just tap on in child. Like
they they girl shoot me up with some
some um tresping
queen. Shoot it. Kevin, you better not
send me that video. [laughter]
A bleaching. A bleaching queen.
Um, girl, they said tap on in. Girl,
they doing the bleaching like tap
paintoop.
I've been telling y'all. And shout out
to my booa
who was talking about um the lighting
that we're seeing with a lot of like
darkkinned celebrities. You know, it's
not them sometimes. Sometimes it's the
photographers. They their photo they'll
take a photo of them and they don't even
look dark skinned. So I'm not
understanding. Baby, I got me a photo
shoot coming up and I know Bardi going
to have me looking bam bam bam. You
going to ban me banned. But yes, we
going to get into Serena Williams.
Speaking of light skins, we going to
talk about Amanda Seals. Amanda Seals is
feeling some type of way. She did the
little Netflix um skit of, you know, she
ain't getting invited to the function.
She ain't get invited for the world tour
for the insecure tour. She like, "Why
y'all invite me?" So, we going to talk
about that. We going to give her a
little bit of light lashes. Just a
little light lashes for the light skin.
Um, and then we going to talk about
these ESPN firings. Everybody getting
the pink slip today. Cam Newton and his
hat. The Mad Hatter is getting the um
pink slip. Ryan uh what's his name? Ryan
Clark, his fine ass got a pink slip,
too. Damn. Everybody going to be at the
food stamp office, girl. I tell y'all we
ain't none of us safe in this recession.
Ain't none of us none of us safe. No,
there safety. What did the hound say on
Game of Thrones? Safety. Come with me,
Arya. I'll take you to say safety. Where
the that there's no safety? Her mother's
dead. Her brother's dead. Her Winterfell
is a pile of rubble. There's no safety.
You dumb. There's no safety. None of us
is safe, girl. All the girls got the
boot. You gonna bam? Disney said, "Girl,
y'all y'all's not making us no money."
This is why we don't need no one
corporation owning all of it. Disney is
is performing at a loss right now.
They're not making a lot of money. Um,
the Disney park is not making a lot of
money. People, we don't got no money.
They trying to squeeze every dollar out
of every other week. Y'all telling us
there's going to be two, three more
dollars to stream the same shows that
y'all only having on eight episode. And
we just asking y'all where's the Tiana
um
the the TV show that we supposed to get.
What happened to that? What happened to
the Princess and the Frog thing, y'all?
We supposed to be getting that at some
What happened? What happened at the New
Orleans? We going to talk about these
ESPN firings. I feel bad for some folks,
but not really. We going to get into
that. Oprah trying to clean it up. We
going to talk about Oprah. Y'all been
whacking Oprah. Y'all whack Oprah so
bad, child. Y'all whacked her bad um
about her comment, you know, comments on
Whitney Houston. She said, "Girl, let me
go talk to the young blacks. Let me go
turn talk turn up with the young knitts
and she go talk to Kiki P. One thing
about it, Kiki Porman. [laughter]
Oh child, her Jackie Washington persona,
she gonna help you. She one thing about
it, Kiki Palmer, she going she Come on
over here, girl. I'm g I'm I'm have
these folk laughing and we gonna be
shucking and driving and they gonna
forget everything that happened. And you
know Oprah, it's working for her. She
came off relatable. She came off like,
"You got a friend in me.
You got a friend in me." Meanwhile, she
own what, uh, 200 acres in Hawaii and
and barely want them folks to get
through the roads. Girl, we going to ban
you. Ban Oprah, you was banned. Girl,
you we saw what you said about Whitney
Houston not too long ago talking to them
good white folks. Now you trying to talk
to the young knitters to get them back
on your side. Child, please. This ain't
the 80s. Um, also we gonna talk about u
Mark Lamont Hill. I don't know if y'all
watch the Joe Button podcast. I don't.
But that clip of ish reading that chat
GPT answer verbatim reading it and
saying this is his source. This is why I
don't argue with folks online. I don't
know if y'all saw that, but this is why
I don't argue with folks online because
this is where they be. This is their
source. They're going straight to
straight to chat GPT. They're going
straight to chat P. Like this is the
answer.
This is why we're talking about how AI
is going to affect us because all it
does is bring information from what's
written online.
somebody can like there's been a report
of a politician um CNN was reporting on
a politician that recognized that he was
not doing well in the polls and some of
the answers and stuff that Chad GPT was
giving the people was from a Wikipedia.
So his opponent, you know, had clear
positions on things and he went and
changed his Wikipedia and did a couple
of articles and stuff. So after he
changed it, his percentage went up
because people were getting the answers.
Like a lot of people will Google, use
Google, which sends you through chat
GPT, GPT, and hey, I want to vote for
this candidate. What are their like what
are their um their policies instead of
reading it because none of us want to
really read, none of us want to go
through all of that. But you know, he's
able to increase his
what's name just by tweaking some
Wikipedia. So that just tells you how
dangerous a AI can be when you can
manipulate the search engine. Um because
people are not doing the research before
they go vote. So it's unfortunate.
[clears throat] It's truly unfortunate.
Um we got to do better with that. Uh so
we're going to talk about that. Mark
Lamont Hill, all of the things. Somebody
sent me a super chat. Let's get into
that. Thank you, Sue. Thank you, Bui.
Thank you. Appreciate that, Boo. Um,
also from I think this is Lettucey
Lettuce. It's been made official that
Megan Stallion is back with Klay
Thompson, her ex. Could you please tell
your fan how you feel about the
situation? About what situation?
I don't Where's the reporting? I can't
see it. I cannot see. I'm legally blind.
Megan didn't put She don't She ain't
take the potato chip back. What is y'all
talking about?
What is y'all talking about? Megan ain't
take that man back. I know. Megan.
Megan, you better not have taken that
man back. If I find out you didn't got
back with the potato chip girl, I'm
going to turn you into guacamole.
Okay. If I find out If I find out that
Megan took Klay Thompson potato chip,
I'mma throw one of them Taylor um
iceberg lettucees at her. Okay. I'mma
I'mma throw lettuce and cabbages. Why?
Right on the stage. Girl, you going to
be bounce what I got. Bounce what you
got. You going to be bouncing on the
lettuce. Okay. Fresh lettuce wrapped up
in some three cheeses.
Y'all ain't telling me that. I don't
believe it. My girl Megan will never do
that. She won't.
Y'all, Megan won't do that. She won't.
She ain't. She Don't tell me.
Don't tell me. My girl,
I don't like it. I don't like it. I
don't like it. I don't like that,
friend. I don't I know. Oh. Oh.
Oh. I hate it. The girls is going to
Google. Let me see.
Did Megan the biggest booty stallion
get Oh, get get back with Klay Thompson.
And all they pulling up is Ricky Smiley.
That ain't no damn source. [laughter]
Oh, Megan Stein and Klay Thompson have
not officially confirmed they are back
together, though rumors are swirling
that they may have secretly reconciled.
Reports indicate that the NBA star has
been spending months trying to repair
the relationship and win her back
following the very public split in
April, which was caused by allegations
that Klay cheated, while Megan publicly
put Klay on blast for infidelity at the
time. Recent gossip suggests that the
two have been spending time together and
their source is Rick is smiling. They
didn't wore that album.
Ask Rick is smiling. That's what GPT
said. Ask Rick is smiling. [laughter]
Those are the rumors. And we already
know what our girl uh Lizo said about
the rumors. All the rumors are true.
Yeah. And you Yeah. Uh that song was
cute. She said no loose lips. Lizo
thought she was on top of the world.
Them folk said, "Girl, okay, [laughter]
girl." Lizo was on top of the no loose
lips. She was talking mess.
And now now she in here bringing Sasha
Santana um [laughter]
to a place he ain't invited to.
H I don't want to believe it. I don't
want to believe it. I don't want to
believe it. I don't want to believe it.
I Megan, but you know what?
As he better be he better go and
apologize.
We better see him show out. But you know
Megan is young. So you know you know the
young girls do stuff like that. How old
is my girl Meg? I'mma let her slide.
Megan like 27.
What's her how what's her age?
Oh,
[laughter]
girl. I I just knew my girl was like
I'm like she in her 20s. Let her make
her mistakes. That thing said 31.
[laughter]
Girl, I was trying. I hope my girl was
like 28 or something like that thing
said girl. She was born in 1995. her as
a 31 years old. Thank y'all. Thank
y'all. Thank y'all. Um,
she I think chat she be we got to check
our sources. She 27.
She is she 27.
She 27. So she 20 at 27 Megan can make
you know she can make those type of
mistakes. I'm so sorry. Like yeah what
the girl be saying? You can never make
me hate me. I hate when folks say, "You
can never make me hate." Shut the hell
up.
Shut the hell up. You can never make me
hate. Girl, shut up before I make you
eat some iceberg lettuce from uh Taylor
Farms. Me going to the Super Bowl. She
going to probably come out cuz I know
Jay-Z Jay-Z going to be at the Super
Bowl. That's why he didn't cut his hair
off. They said we don't we we we are
past kneeling and we pass afro. So, we
want you to be up here. You know, you
going to sing for the white good white
folks come February of 2027. He going to
be up there. He going to be so happy. He
going to have to bring everybody out in
their mama cuz ain't nobody coming out
just to see Jay-Z by himself.
But you know,
I don't know, child. I'm just not a I'm
not a fan of I'm just not a fan of
Jay-Z. I'm just not. Girl, I don't see
it for her. Um I just don't. She been 27
for five years just like Doge Cat and
Cardi. [laughter]
Leave my girl alone. Not too much. Not
too much on my girl. Big the big
stallion, not the little stallion. The
big stallion.
But yeah, let's go ahead and get to the
pieces. Um Kevin, have you found a
bleaching queen? A bleaching A bleaching
girl. [laughter]
A bleaching girl. I know I can find it.
A bleaching queen.
A
bleaching queen. Original bleaching girl
rubbing on the cream. [laughter]
I found it. Oh. Oh, you said you
bleaching girl. [laughter]
Girl.
Oh my god. I hate it for my sister. I
hate it.
A bleaching cream. my bleaching girl.
Rubbing on the cream. [laughter]
You can use a bleaching. Um, so yes,
unfortunately,
Serena Williams,
you know, there was a I, you know, I
hate to talk about I hate to talk about
the black women's. I really do hate to
talk about the black women's. I really
do. Uh but you know the girls, Miss
Serena Wiggins had shared this video.
Pull it up. She shared this video and um
she was dancing
and um you know she was showing she got
the moves and you know she lost weight.
You know she's been doing a lot. I'm on
row. I'm on road. I'm on road. You know
hey girl you know what you need to do.
You know what? You
We know. We know what you need. This
This text I just got, I'm screaming. My
girl is like two days late.
Girl, what is going
Oh my god. Um,
child. But
if she wants to lose weight, like I I
don't even care. She She been on roll.
She's on row. She's doing her stuff. I I
I I frankly don't even care at this
point. Um,
but I'm kind of confused. Like this is
what Serena Williams used to look like.
That she used to girl no music now.
I does ro is it one of the side effects
of being on road turn into a white
woman?
Like I don't
I don't get it.
Girl, is this Tyler playing in the
background?
like she looks
she look like a white girl. I'm sorry.
I She look like a white girl.
And Serena Williams, I really do feel
bad for her because she you know folks
said she look like a man. They have
talked about her like I remember the
days when they used to the men used to
talk about how ugly she was and how dark
she was and all of the thing. I really
hate that. You know, she she got a white
man and you know,
I don't know. Maybe it's AI. I don't
know. But this don't look like I
And a You know what, y'all? In all
seriousness, a lot of our favorite
celebrities have been looking like this.
A lot of our favorite celebrities have
starting to lighten up. And I I
it's not just their face. Their whole
body is light. Now there is something
going on. There is some money being
spent. I don't care what nobody say.
There's they are bleaching. They might
not be doing the rubbing on the cream.
They might not be rubbing on the queen
on the cream. Uh but they they doing
something.
They they might not be they something is
going on and we got to talk about it.
Like I hate this for everybody. What is
going on? They a bleaching cream.
>> Original bleaching girl
cream.
>> Original bleaching girl.
>> Original bleaching girl. [laughter]
Uh I'm Ailia Banks. Um tooth to the
left. Um
[laughter]
baby them hoes slide to the left. One
hop this time.
[laughter]
Aelia Banks is she is something else
child. But yeah, my girl she you know
um
I don't I I want to know the role come
with side effects like this.
I [laughter] I got some questions
because why does she like what's going
on?
Like
I always thought Serena Williams um was
beautiful.
I always thought she was beautiful. I've
always thought it. But
I just Why all my girl and you not tell
weight loss? Yeah, I think some
sometimes when you do lose weight, you
will see some changes in your face. But
girl, not like that. Like I have lost
some weight. My face is still dark.
Like I have some hyperpigmentation in
some areas and stuff. But girl, I ain't
out here looking like if I start looking
like that. I want y'all to start bring
up the allegations. Is you bleaching?
Is you bleaching? If if I start going
that shade, like three shades light. I
want y'all to ask me, girl, I might need
to take a look at my peel bottle and see
what the side effects is giving. I might
need to Hey, Big Tarvy. Hey girl, does
this is side effects of me lightening up
and turning to white girls? Like I I
need to I got questions.
I got if you start to see me like
[laughter]
my skin start getting light like you
need to say, "Hey, is you bleaching?"
[laughter]
You going to have to ask me. You need to
You need to be concerned like Justin, is
you bleaching? A bleaching girl.
Bleaching girl rubbing on the cream. You
need to put that in my chat. But a
bleaching grab.
[laughter]
A bleaching grab. I want y'all I give
y'all permission. A bleaching grab.
The bleaching rubbing on the cream. You
need to tell me like is it giving is it
giving a bleach?
Tell me girl.
>> Girl rubbing out cream.
>> Original bleaching girl.
>> Original bleaching girl. Like ask them
girls. Is Justin, did you bleaching?
Rub it on the cream. I love what she
said. Rub it on the cream. We love some
cream.
Kevin, wait. [laughter]
Oh my god, girl. [clears throat]
What is this? What did Kevin make,
y'all?
>> It's not a bleaching girl. If you rub
out cream
and is looking at you like, [laughter]
>> you think he's bleaching?
Charlene is bleaching.
>> I've never bleached
>> original bleaching girl.
Nola
immediate cla volume party. [laughter]
>> Charlemagne's mixing.
>> Got to play it one more time.
>> Oh, bleaching. Girl, if you're rubbing
out the cream,
envy is looking at you like [laughter]
>> rub it on the cream.
Charlmagne's bleaching.
>> I've never bleached
>> original bleaching girl [laughter]
naughty
immediate cla volume party [laughter]
Charlemagne's mixing
>> girl. I need to find that video of that
woman doing the um doing the uprising.
She said, "Oh, I you got it. I got She
was putting white paint all on her." She
said, "Oh, still left." I [laughter]
like this is what this g volume 30 um
original bleaching girl rubbing on the
cream. I
you know what I in all seriousness I I I
feel bad for the folks like I feel bad
for people who feel like they have to
resort to things like this. Um, and you
know, I I'm laughing at it for now, but
I do think it's a very serious subject.
Um, and I I I have to kind of laugh from
like crying because
these folks will make you hate yourself
enough that you will go and start doing
these things. And I think a lot of
people are guilty of it more than they
want to admit. Um, and I think that's
it's very uncomfortable conversation to
have.
Um, the way people talk about their
hair. I was having a conversation this
weekend, one of one of my friends who
said that he wanted to grow his locks
out, but he didn't want to go through
the ugly stage. He didn't want and I'm
like the ugly stage is just your natural
hair growing.
Like the way we describe our like this
is what our hair looks like. I feel like
we're we're going back. Um, I'm not
seeing I'm seeing a lot of folks now
praise people for cutting their hair.
Um, the natural hair care movement was
actually was one of my favorite. We talk
about doing a quote unquote woke era. I
love the natural hair movement. Um, but
I feel like we've went back. Like I I I
feel bad hearing young teenagers talk
about their hair and their bodies. they
are hypo hypo um hyper critical of
themselves and I think that's because of
social media. I feel like colorism it
never left but I feel like it's gotten
worse. Um and we see that we see it in
the media that we consume. We see it in
the commercials. Um every TV show that
we see it is a black dark-kinned dad
with a white mama. I am so tired. Even
in back rooms, he had a white mama wi
with from I mean on back what was back
rooms he had a white wife from a white
wife. Every time I see a black main
character, they have a white wife and
it's always biracial curly kids. I'm so
tired I'm so tired of seeing the
biracial kids in the Acura and the
Cadillac and the um and the car
commercials and the Cheerios
commercials. Just like my god, how many
more light-skinned kids we got? That's
why I be telling y'all the folks the the
gays that be, you know, go viral and
post their children on on Tik Tok, they
cannot wait to brush their children 4C
hair. Um, is that the hair texture?
That's what's the loose hair texture.
What's that? Is that 4C? They cannot
wait to brush their hair on on the on
the Instagram on the TW. They want y'all
to know, look at my baby and they light
skin and they and they good hair. They
can't. They might not be saying good
hair no more, but trust and believe they
showing you because they believe this is
good hair. This is what hair's texture
is supposed to look like. 3C. Thank
y'all for Thank y'all for clarifying.
Y'all know I don't know child. I don't
be going to the beauty shop like that,
but 3C. I said 4C. 4C is actually my
stuff.
This is 4C. Is it 4C? Hey, this 4C.
Yeah, that 3C. But I, you know, I
remember when you used to go on YouTube
and look at natur when you used to type
in black women natural hair, it would
nothing be the most videos that got the
most views were light-kinned women. Tell
me I'm wrong, y'all. Tell me I'm wrong.
When you used to go and type it in, you
used to see nothing but light-skinned
women doing curls. That's all you used
to see. I was like, girl, my god. Like,
they used to have the most views. They
used to get the They used to be the ones
getting all the endorsements. They used
to be the ones being able to to sell all
the stuff. Like I remember like my god.
Like we talking about natural hair. What
the hell is this? Why is this the only
representation that we seeing is
light-skinned girl, biracial girls doing
they little white woman wig? They
washing their hair. Oh my god. I'm ready
to go. [laughter]
Like that's all you saw. And you seeing
that re reemerge in Tik Tok. When I be
looking up locks, all I see is
light-skinned boys. Every time I look up
locks, like lock styles for men, I be
seeing even AI videos of light-skinned
men.
I don't want to see that. My hair is she
whoop she folded up like Claudia's bob.
Whoop. And I'm okay with that. I love my
fy hair. I love it. Period.
Period. She's strong as hell. as she
should be and I'm going to get her
whipped and cut and tucked this Sunday.
Well, this Saturday, but that's all you
see. Like the girls in back, you know,
they slapping these wigs on that don't
look nothing close to their hair
texture. It's no sh I I get I'm not
dragging it. The men do it too. When
they hair ain't done, they going to wear
a hat. They going to wear a do-agg. The
young boys, they wearing hoodies over
their head and a ski mask because they
don't like the way their hair look. They
be painting their hair on. Everybody,
the boys, they 16 years old. Just paint
it. Just paint it down. Just paint it
down. And y'all be out here trying to
drag the black girls for getting their
wigs done all the time. And y'all be
waking up, put permanent marker on
there. Like, girl, I I don't know if I
need to go take you to the dry erase
board. I can literally take your head
and do a math equation. I can literally
take your head and and and pass algebra,
too.
like just using your scalp. I can write
out I can do some slopes and stuff. I
can, you know, I don't know nothing
about math. I can't make no jokes about
math. I have no like I I don't know no m
what's that stuff you used to do? Xom
xyz
[laughter]
I don't know.
I I don't know.
I can't come on a joke. I don't even
know no match. What is it? Uh, please
excuse my dear aunt Sally.
Period. Uh, [laughter]
uh, yeah. Like, please. Exc. Yes. Come
on. Y equals. Come on. Oh, she's Come
on, y'all. Coming in here. Where? Where
the math scholars in? They They coming.
The math scholars is coming in here,
child. All I know is please excuse my
dear aunt Sally. Please excuse her.
[laughter]
That's all I
That's all I know is Miss Sally. Girl,
Miss Sally. Miss Sally up. Miss Sally
down. Please excuse her. She getting
around. Hey. Oh, Miss is getting up.
[laughter]
I'mma let y'all have that one. X is the
slope. She is cuz she go down the slide.
No Ruchia. Period. Okay. Y'all talking
about Romas. Ain't that the name of a um
ain't that the name of some vacuum
cleaner on the ground or something? A
Oh, Greg, y'all doing too much. This is
not the act. This is not the SAT. Like,
please. What? Roy,
[laughter]
y'all remember that video, that episode
of Roy and um Tammy getting into it?
They both was like, [laughter] "This is
what I'm doing with y'all right now."
Girl, you going to ban me? Ban.
Okay. But Serena Williams, very serious
subject. Um, the bleaching cream. I like
I told y'all, Tiffany Pa, Tiffany Paula
used to I remember watching Tiffany
Paula on New York. She don't look like
that no more. Tiff like she's had some
work done. She's But Tiffany look
light-skinned now. Tiff New York looks
light-skinned. And I remember seeing it
a couple years ago. I said, "Is my girl
bleaching?" I remember saying it in in
private. I was like, "Is my is Tiffany
Paula bleaching?" Like, you don't want
to accuse of bleaching cuz I'm not
bleaching. I'm not y'all. But Tiffany
Paula does not She's not dark skinned no
more. She's not dark skinned. Um,
so now I'm fa Let me see if I can find
this video because
one thing about y'all, one thing about
Maya, they going to wake it up each and
every time. They going to wake Maya
going to wake I appreciate folks like
Maya cuz Maya don't mind, you know, hey,
I'm gonna say the stuff that makes y'all
feel uncomfortable. Like I know this is
an uncomfortable conversation, but we
got to have it. So Maya posted this
today.
Um, and it made so much sense.
>> Oh, let me
>> use lighting in this day and time. Like
this is Kelly Roland, but her complexion
looks completely unrecognizable.
Mind you, people are saying like, "Oh,
since our cameras have gotten sharper,
that's why like people you can see their
complexion clearly or whatever stupid
reason." But look at how
>> this looks so much better. And this is
photographed in the 2000s. Like this is
a camera where you can see her
undertones. you can see her complexion
very clearly. It's not washing her out.
And it's not even just a Kelly Roland
thing. Like I see a lot of celebrities
that will work with these like really
high-end photographers who will use
these lightings and it's literally
taking you to a completely different
complexion than how we all rec recognize
or remember you. And I think that it's
because we live in a time where colorism
is just so prevalent and so heavy that
pretty much everyone is lightening their
skin. Even if you look at filters, like
a lot of filters just naturally lighten
you because people assume that you want
to be lighter. Nobody thinks that we
want to get photos where you can
actually see our undertone and our real
complexion. Everybody wants to use these
damn lightings, lights that will make
you look like a completely
unrecognizable person. Stop working with
these kinds of photographers cuz it's
just like it's scary. No.
>> Yeah, I completely agree. Um Snap
Snapchat did that was notorious for
that. Um, I've seen colorism and I wish
I can find it. There is this AI image
that's circul circulating on fa Facebook
[clears throat]
and it was about what type of stud do
you like and it was like like what
versions of stud you like um and they
had the skinny stud that had like a
short haircut and then they had a stud
light-kinned like they started off the
studs being light-kinned but when they
started to gain weight
um they made them darker like as They
got thicker, they made them dark skin,
and they added more tattoos, and they
changed their hair texture. And I saw
that same AI um picture of what type of
dark skin, what type of man do you want?
And when when they got fatter, they had
them as dark skin. Um and I wish
I wish um I w You saw that? Oh my god. I
wish that I can show that to y'all right
now. Let me see if I can find it really
really quick. Um,
let me see. AI stud. Let me see if it
come up.
Let me see.
Girl, what
stood? Let me see. My god. Let me see if
I can find Twitter is a terrible place
to find stuff now. Um,
girl, I'm not going to be able to find
it. AI stood.
Girl, so much stuff. I wish I can find
it.
I wish I can find it. But you all, if
you all see, y'all know what I'm talking
about. Uh, you saw it on threads. You
saw it on threads, period. So, I was
like, what is what what are we doing?
Like we saw that with the um the fruit.
Remember the fruit show that was coming
on Tik Tok and they had the you you can
tell that the the fruit was
light-skinned. The fruit was
light-skinned. But when it came to the
ones that are supposed to be the
knitters, they were eggplants. They were
dark skin. They look aggressive and all
of that. I'm like, girl, what is going
on?
What are we doing? What is this for?
Some am I late to the live? Yeah, girl.
You like 38 minutes late. It's okay
though. Come on in. But y'all remember
them fruits and stuff, child. They had
the strawberries. She was She had a
lighter voice. You can tell she was
light-skinned. Then the the dark skin
eggplants. Ah, we going to come and
snatch your cookie.
What?
And the folks don't be thinking, they
don't think that this Oh, you know, this
is what it is. I'm telling y'all,
there's so much colorism. It's so vamp.
Um, it's it's so I said vamp, I'm
thinking about Wendy Williams. a little
vamp uh but it's so rampant that I know
101 15 years from now we're gonna be
looking back at it and I love like I
love Zenaia. I love Zenaia. Um I I love
her characters. I loved her as Ru. I
think Ru is my favorite character she's
ever played. I didn't grow up watching
her. I was an adult by then. But Zenaia
is the type of black woman that the
world wants to see. And I appreciate her
conversations about colorism and I
appreciate her talking about how hard it
is for black women, but Zenaia is she is
benefiting from looking close to a white
woman.
There's a reason why she's the top fe
like she's in every box office like
she's every movie is a box box office
hit. She's touching things that
dark-kinned black women will never be
able to experience in this current like
day and age.
I've not seen the Odyssey. And every
movie we see Zenaia in is with a white
man. Every movie we see she is with a
white man.
Every movie. It's like the only time
she's ever was with Malcolm and Marie.
You're not going to see her do that.
You're not. You You just This is what
This is the blackness that we want to
see. I think we have to understand that
this is the black that they want to see.
And there's they are very intentional on
it. So they might not say, "Oh girl, we
we only like light-skinned." They not
they don't have to say that. They can
move in a way that you got to read
between the lines.
Like all these black actresses out here
hungry for opportunities. All these
dark-kinned black actresses, you know,
hungry for opportunities and stuff. And
then the only person they able to get a
job from is Tyler Perry. and he moved
like he's saving all the black women
while also demonizing them with
characters that caricatures that he be
doing for his movies. Like it's just
there is nowhere to go. So Tyler Perry
is being shot up like he cares. Like no
girl, you're just the last stop. Like we
don't want I actually don't want to go
here. I actually don't want to eat here,
but I actually don't have a choice. So I
don't know. I'm ranting. I'm up I'm I'm
pressed. I'm upset. All the things. Um,
but it is what it is and I'm not
surprised that she married a white man.
But next next question, Tama. Um, but
Serena Williams, shout out to you.
Whatever. Moving on. Um, Amanda Seal,
speaking of light-skinned women who are
Amanda Seals.
My god. Today, Amanda, I just
So, Amanda Seals
posted this. I I I'm I'mma put her on.
Where she at? The girls love they love
them some Amanda Hills.
So, not too long ago
when it came to her talking about the
reunion,
this this is a Amanda Seals. She hates
the establishment because she wants to
be a part of the establishment. She
posted this five days ago. Some
throwbacks to celebrate 10 years of
insecurity.
So, um, this next shot is going to be on
Isa's mom and
>> Issa looks amazing. This is her. This is
This is Amanda Seals
5 days five days ago. And now this is
Amanda Seals yesterday. [music]
>> It's fine. It's fine.
It's fine.
I ain't never seen somebody that hates
the party but wants to get inside.
Like [laughter]
you hate the club but you want to get
inside.
I wouldn't I
girl, this up here would have told me
not to do this. I wouldn't even done I
would never have posted this, Amanda. I
would have sent this to my friends. I
would have posted I wouldn't even have
posted this on my fa
because this is like she she wants to be
included in the party.
She wants to be included in the party so
bad. Like she wants to be a part. And
yeah, it's fine. IT'S FINE. IT'S FINE.
IT'S FINE. It's fine. It's
It's fine.
>> Derek
[music]
because this is who she truly is.
This is This is She She could not wait.
I I bet she had her white boy in her
bedroom. I need to get me a white boy.
I've been thinking about getting me a
white boy. I've seen somebody have a
white boy in their house. I'm like,
"This is actually smart cuz I I wouldn't
mind."
But
This is This is a man of seals.
This is a man of seals.
This
Oh, what? What women? Oh, Amanda.
Girl, please go sit down, sister. You
are annoying as hell. Like and this is
why I have to check in with myself
because there are people Amanda Seals
has 2 million people following her and
people gassing her up.
People are gassing Amanda Seals up like
[laughter]
you you not wrong queen.
YOU NOT WANT YOU not wrong queen. They
should have you. Why would you want to
be a part? You just got through whacking
Issa. You've been whacking Issa Ray for
years. Why would you I wouldn't even be
celebrating. I wouldn't be posting
nothing. I wouldn't be posting nothing.
I would say happy birthday. Happy
birthday. Happy 10 years. But to post
back to back, girl, them folks is on
your mind. Y always on my mind. So yeah,
Insecure is going on um tour right now.
Um they announced that they're going on
tour. Um,
let me see if I can find the um,
so this is
>> great.
>> All right, that's a wrap for today.
Thank you everyone.
>> Okay, great.
Hey, do you want to go on tour?
>> Yeah. Okay, cool. I mean, boo.
[music]
And people are asking why why is
insecure going on tour? What they doing
the tour for? Because they need some
money. Come on y'all. Let's stop
playing. Like we can be honest. They
need some money. Why? And I honestly
don't blame them. Like girl, we need
some money and y'all love Insecure. So
we going to sell it to y'all. Like hey
we going on tour.
We I mean Issa Ray is fighting a like
she's talking about this. Um Jesse Woo
interview her when she came to Atlanta
earlier this year and how hard it is to
get projects green lit.
We're seeing Disney lay folks off.
They're
not greenlighting these black show. We
ain't seen no black shows.
We like the black shows that they oh
like they don't even want to promote the
black shows. You see what happened with
Iron Hard? They barely wanted to promote
that. Disney was like, "Oh, I guess
we'll I guess we'll do this." Cuz you
see what happened with um the um the
Blood and the Bone. Um they they casted
Amanda Steinberg. Why in the hell would
you cast Amanda Styberg and her
and all all of the conversation about
her taking these um these roles that are
supposed to be for darkkinned women? Why
would y'all do that? Like to me, I would
just say, "Girl, you I would even sign
you." No, ma'am. I would have in my
contract that you will not be having a
man of Steinberg playing my very playing
a dark-skinned person in my movie.
Like why would you? So this is what this
is what Hollywood and I I'm telling
y'all Hollywood will push that they'd be
like well we need a light-skinned person
in here. Them white folks be in that
room. Well, we need a light-skinned
person in here. We need we just can we
can we soften it up? Can we just soft?
It's a little too black. It's a little
too black.
I'm not supporting it. I don't want to.
That I I ain't gonna lie. Looking at it,
I was like, "This [ __ ] look goofy as
hell.
It just does not It just The soul looks
like it's gone. It looks soulless. I
hate the wigs. I hate the wigs. I don't
know. Maybe after the color grading and
stuff, I want to support it, but I'm
tired of supporting the bare minimum
just because I'd rather support smaller
creators who who don't have to go back
on their word to be a part of this.
I I'd rather do that. I I rather support
smaller creators that are here making
smaller projects. Um and they don't have
to sell themselves to to do that. Like I
I'm I'm so sorry.
So yeah. Um cuz we don't need to be a
part of Hollywood like this. If we had
to sacrifice ourselves to be a part of
Hollywood, then was it worth it? Was it
worth it? Um, flipping reverse it. So,
yeah, Amanda Seals, Insecure. I
understand why they going on tour. And I
might buy a ticket. I like Issa Ray. I
think she's a brilliant, beautiful
person. I would love to talk to her.
So, yeah. I'm, you know, I'm buying a
ticket. I'm pretty sure they ain't
number $60. I'll be going up. Hey.
Period. So, let's move on to other news.
Other news is um
it's the girls like speaking of firings
[laughter]
>> just my finances
>> like
>> the budgeting you see how I am
>> ESPN and gave the girl the boot
>> the boot let me say hey to some of these
super chats it's been made
oh you already answered that I already
answered that oh I already talked about
that it's on Google.
They spent time in Mexico recently and
she posted photos to prove it. Huh. I
don't know about that. K. Thompson
splashed her with expensive gifts for
the past two months to order to have her
come back apparently. Oh lord, I'm
screaming. Y'all is crazy in these
comments. Will the complexions be
separated by according to class?
Well, [sighs and gasps]
yes. Um,
yeah. So yeah, ESPN is is handing out
pink slips. They handing them out bad.
They handing them out bad. And they got
my boy Ryan Clark. They got my baby.
They got Ryan Clark. I'm like, Ryan
Clark was the only good thing over at
ESPN. I love to see his conversation. I
love when he had called out when he be
calling out the raccoons. I'll be here
for it. Ryan Clark was let go by ESPN
yesterday in the middle of a live show
and TMZ has learned how it all went
down. A source with direct knowledge to
TMZ, Ryan was going to be notified on
Tuesday that he was part of a mass
layoff. But on Monday, the network was
made aware that a report was about to
drop about the former NFL player being
laid off. The report was going to be
published while Ryan was filming NFL
Live and a call had to be made. How
should he find out? We're told t es We
were told ESPN honcho decided to get
ahead of the news until Ryan during a
commercial break rather than him seeing
alert on his phone. Ryan did not come
back on the air after being informed he
was being let go. Obviously, this news
rattled him and we're told both Ryan
ESPN agreed it was better not to return.
This is so messed up.
This is messed up.
Like, girl, them folks like,
[snorts]
you know what? You just
This is so messed up. Like, I cannot
uh Cam Newton got the boot. A couple of
white folks that I do not care about got
the boot, too. Um I don't care about
[ __ ] Newton being chopped. Good. Um
period.
Uh but Ryan uh Clark dropped a
statement. This is where he said on
Twitter, "Baby, this picture is Oh, this
is the throwback child. Is this his
college picture?"
That man fine. Sending prayers and love
to all those laid off today by ESPN. So
many of you have poured your life into
that company. I know how you're feeling
right now. My hope is is as this door
closes, another opens for you all. God
bless.
Yeah, I hate this for her. Um,
it's messed up to fire somebody while
they like to get in the news while they
on air is wild.
Like that is wild. Like, hey girl, you
we found you. Like this is wild.
And that man used to have them he used
to have them suits on. Child Ryan Clark
used to he used to have them suits on.
Do you hear me? He used to look good.
and that that um that beard.
Let let's
let me see. Let's put Ryan Clark on the
on Oh,
that's not Ryan Clark.
That's not him.
That's not Mr. Clark. [laughter]
That's not Mr. Clark. Wake up, Mr. West.
[laughter]
This ain't Mr. Clark.
My bad. I That's the wrong I'm so sorry,
y'all. My My bad. My bad. Let me see if
I can find the the right picture. Mr.
Clark, I'm so sorry. You know, I be
getting the black men confused. That's a
stud. That's not Okay, Mr. Clark. That's
Mr. Clark. Period. Mr. Clark, look at
like look at the suit. Look at this
double breasted suit. Wait, is this a
double breasted suit? I don't know. Um,
look at this man. It's a good man,
Savannah. a good man. Um, but yeah, they
they they let me man go.
Um, Cam Newton, I guess he gonna be
interviewing more folks cuz baby,
she got the boot, too. All of them. Like
Disney has let go of some of Pixar staff
as well, too. They've been cutting. They
said, "Girl, all y'all got to go. All
y'all got to go.
We got to make money." I'm telling
y'all, Disney is in performing in the
red. Their movies are not doing well.
That's why they got Captain America
coming back like he's we need America
and it's Captain America asking for this
this movie Doom. Not I Doom. I'm
thinking about Doomsday.
It's giving that y'all need some coin.
It's giving that y'all need some some
fun, some some money. Like y'all need to
figure it out. Like y'all need a cash
grab. This whole movie is giving cash
grab. You know, I I I don't know what to
feel about it. Like, I'mma go see it,
but it's giving cash grab. It's giving
cash grab. And is it going to be good?
I'mma see. We going to see. But this is
giving y'all need a cash grab.
Like, they they said, "Hey girl, let's
go get all the other folks that people
care about. Let's bring Iron Man back as
Doom." Like, it's just giving, "Hey
girl, we need some coin." Like, the
girls is not buying into the other
stuff. We need to reset.
We need to reset.
Um,
so yeah, I hate that for everybody.
Let's move on. Um, let's talk about
I just want to go ahead and talk about
Lamar Lamont Hill and ish. Do anybody
watch the Joe Button podcast? Please, if
y'all watch the Joe Buddton podcast,
please tell me in the chat. Did y'all
watch this latest episode?
Yeah, I'm not I'm I'm kind of like I
didn't get no chills, but I do want to
see it. The new Avengers. I don't know.
I I want to see it, but I don't know.
So, I watched the clips, too. And this
clip.
Oh, Ish is a dummy. I'm so I normally
don't call folks dummies, but ish is a
dummy.
Like Ish is a dummy. So
is
being challenged by
>> what happened was we didn't have no
>> girl. Why is that playing?
That's dumb. It's like some you just
like you're dumb.
>> Why is stuff playing in the background?
What is that? Uhuh. This is Stop. I
don't know what's going on with that.
It's getting spooky. I'll come back.
Like, but girl, what
why is it doing like girl, why is y'all
playing background stuff? I got it on
pause.
So, they were talking about Jay-Z.
There's a clip going viral of Mouse.
Y'all remember Mouse from um The
Grapevine? mouse was having a
conversation with some I don't know who
his name I don't know I think his name
is Memphis Bleak I don't know who that
dude I don't know maybe I don't know I
look good uh but
they were talking like mouse was saying
like they're disappointed in Jay-Z and
the Target um thing that he did and I've
talked about that I think Jay-Z working
with target
Jay-Z didn't have to but this is the
same Jay-Z who sat next to Ivanka Trump
and Eric
I mean Jared Kushner, they do not care.
Like Jay-Z is a sellout. Point blank.
Period. He's a sellout. And now he's
trying to clean it up that he's not a
sellout. Oh, y'all pocket y'all
politicking and pocket watching. No
girl, you're a sellout. You're a
sellout. Like, you're a sellout. We We
ain't get nothing. So
Mark
is arguing with Ish. Ish is trying to
say that the Target boycott is over. So
why are we even talking about that the
Target boycott is over with and Mark is
saying the Target boycott is not over
with? People are saying the Target
boycott is over with because of Jamal
Bryant. Griffin ass. Jamal Bryant said
that the boycott was over. Jamal Bryant
was not the person who spearheaded or
started or asked for the boycott of none
of that. He jumped on that bandwagon to
get attention because he's attention
hungry knitter. like he's a knitter.
>> He's a knitter.
>> Jamal Bryan, the ultimate knitter.
>> Um,
so
is reading a Google AI like he's like,
"Okay, well, where are you getting your
sources from? Like what's where are you
getting your source from to talk about?"
And this man, he pulling out his phone
like he a child.
Like he is a child. and reading like I
just everything about this gives so
childish to me like this cannot be no
grown man reading AI like this
>> pardon me including racial
>> I got to start it from the beginning
data because it's
it's AI and he just explained this
this man read he and he asked me said
hey can you site your sources
Can you site your sources? He's like,
"Oh, this is chat GPT."
The latest report is that the boycott
was still on.
If you write a paper, you can't just
site AI. You You can't at some point you
could even site Wikipedia. You have to
like where did you get this from?
Where's where's your sources at? Now,
shout out to Lavvenia Hammond that
taught me my 12th grade um English
honors teacher. I now understand why you
was like, "No, you need to site your
sources." I now I now understand that 26
years later. [laughter]
Well, before but shout out to Lavine.
Was it 26 years? How long I've been out
of high school? 21.
I don't know. I don't do I'm not good at
math. It's been 21. Yeah. Where where
like where are your references? Like
where is where are where are you getting
this information from? This man, he
read.
The moment he was, the moment he started
reading like that, I knew he didn't know
what he was talking about. There was no
confidence in how he was reading. He was
not projecting. He cuz he sounded
uncomfortable.
You can you can 26 year old. Leave me
alone.
I'm being funny. Uh but
you can tell in how he was reading.
This is one thing I cannot stand that
men do. When I used to work at
restaurants, men never want to speak up.
I used to hate it. I used to hate when
men sat at my table cuz they were Let me
get the the chicken alfredo.
Chicken Alfredo.
Huh? Speak up. I can't hear you. Then
the women have to speak up for their
man. Yeah. He want the chicken Alfredo
and he want extra sauce and can we get
some bread sticks? Like why this woman
got TO SPEAK FOR YOU? CAN'T TALK. I
THOUGHT YOU WEAR THE PANTS IN a
relationship. They just be mumbling. I
hate it. so much y'all talk like little
boys and I and granted some of them some
of y'all do have social anxiety. I get
that. But I'm talking about men in
general. Men in general do not want to
open their mouth. They so they they
don't want to talk. I have to teach my
little brother that like, hey, you don't
talk to me when we at this at the
McDonald's or whatever. You need to tell
these folk what you want. I want a
burger with with no pickles, no onions,
just cheese. You need to tell these
folk. learn how to speak up for
yourself. These men are they boys.
They're kids. And I'm not going to let
my brother be no little boy forever. But
yeah, like this is you can tell by the
way he was speaking.
>> It's possibly over. I'm saying that I
the prominent local organizer
organizers.
>> He just he not confident. The prominent
organizer like you read that stuff. This
is you arguing your point. This is what
you get paid to do. You literally make
money. Then he got mad because y'all be
talking about I got a white girlfriend
and I'm not pro black. You're not. I'm
gonna tell you, you know, you're not pro
black. You got a white girlfriend and
you got white politics. You are not pro
black. You are in fact not pro black.
Period. In the discussion. There's too
many of y'all with white partners who
who got shaky politics. So hell no. We
even got to talk about your white
partner. We ain't even got to bring that
up. The lie detector test determined
that was a lie. It don't even matter
that y'all got a It don't even matter.
You are you white by definition.
This just extra that you would We not
surprised that you got a white
girlfriend, girl. We We We listening to
you talking. WE NOT SURPRISED THAT YOU
GOT A WHITE GIRLFRIEND, GIRL. We
listening to how you talk. You talk like
you a snow bunny chaser. So, no, we not.
We know them type of stuff work with
white women's. You can't talk like that
with no black woman. She going to be
looking upside your head like, "What is
you talking about? What are you talking
about?
Like, what are you talking about?" So
ish, we know you got a white woman. We
not surprised by that. We know you been
eating more than Pizza Hut. We know
you've been eating snow bunnies. Like,
y'all don't talk about me cuz I got a
white girlfriend. You need to grow up.
If you out here, if you out here getting
defensive because everybody's telling me
I'm not black because I have a white
partner.
Sister,
y'all y'all
y'all need to grow up. You need If you
My God, y'all questioning my blackness.
We can never get into the real
conversation that we got to coddle folks
feelings. Y'all are talking about I'm
not being black because I have a white
mama. Oh my god. Y'all talking about me.
I don't have a white mama. Like we can
never get to the conversation. We got to
c y'all feelings.
We got to c y'all feelings each and
every time. Like no sister, I'm not.
And the ones who be overperforming
because they got a non-black partner or
white partner, I be smelling it too. The
saxophones be loud with y'all too cuz I
be
>> sister if you this if you this pro all
of that. If you this pro if you are this
pro like I don't support this this
place.
I don't support this place. That means
you never eating there. That means you
never eaten there. I'm sorry. The way
your relationship shows up says a lot.
Your relationship, your dating life show
like shows where your politic lies. I'm
so sorry. I'm so sorry. If you date
nothing but light-skinned folks,
I don't know what to tell you.
I don't know what to tell you. If every
one of your girlfriends been
light-skinned, I don't know what to tell
you.
I don't know. I asked you. Is it a
coincidence? I asked you.
So, I don't know, girl. Like, I'm not
going to be calling your feelings. We
can't get into I can't talk about the
real thing. That's That's what's wrong
with the conversation about um Bob and
Monae. And I hate that Silky had to
apologize because Silky was not wrong.
Yeah, y'all are y'all are swirls. Y'all
are, you know, y'all are Oreos. I That's
not an offensive word. I'm so sorry.
Y'all are not Nobody's getting lynched
by being called no Oreo. I'm so sorry.
I'm I'm I'm tired of calling y'all damn
feeling. You are an Oreo. Your ass is an
oreo. Y'all got 10 partners and all of
them white. Your last five partners have
been white. You are an Oreo. The white
people love you. It's not exactly your
fault. But the white audience love you.
There's a reason why the white folks
like Simone and they don't like on your
nerve. Cuz Simone, they don't see the
Simone as no damn black woman. They see
her as a white woman trapped in a black
woman body. Let's be honest.
The way Simone be cosplaying as a black
person,
Ana ain't got to do all that. And I
think Anya got a black a white partner.
Anya nerve got a white partner. But you
know what? I I can I can testify that
Ana like being around black folks. I can
testify to that. And I don't care about
Ana because I'm like, I don't care about
her having no white partner. I'm like,
"Oh, girl, I know how she moving. I know
how she shaking." But y'all, I know
it'll never be a chance in here y'all
have a black partner. And if they do,
they whitewash and they DEI hire for
you. Period. That's all I got. Mona
exchange
child. Please,
please, please. Um, her and Bob like
Silky was not wrong.
Like the way Silky had to talk about
some of the things that she experienced.
It's a child. Jada Essence Hall. I think
Jada Essaul is one of the most talented
drag queens that has came out of
RuPaul's drag race and they do not give
her her things and her tins because Jada
like being around black folks. Jada
likes black folks and she do not playing
in white games and they do not she do
not play. She don't them white folks
love oh you date white people too. They
they gonna say it out loud but they said
oh my gosh you date white people you're
just like me. You're just like me.
You're trying to what? My girl Kisha
Cole said I'm just like you.
Take care of my just like you.
My throat going to be I just want to be
happy.
[laughter]
Uh but yeah, my throat tired, child.
They didn't wor that outage. Um what
else is going on? Uh, oh, we got 1,600
people in the chat today. Shout out
y'all is in the chat. Let's move on. Um,
let's talk about Oprah and Kiki Palmer.
So, Oprah went on the um Kiki Palmer
show.
Oprah said, "Girl, y'all is whacking me
a little too hard." Y, who is this? I
know who is this person.
child to
Oprah said, "Girl, y'all is whacking me
too hard."
Oprah said, "Y'all whacking me about
that Whitney Houston stuff. Let me go
talk to a Whitney Houston impersonator."
[snorts]
Oprah said, "Y'all is whacking me way
too hard for telling them white folks
that Whitney Houston was relapsing. Let
me go talk to a a Whitney Houston
impersonator. [laughter]
Let me go talk to Akila in the be
[laughter]
girl.
Oprah said, "Girl, let me go talk to
Whitney Houston." Reincarnate.
[laughter]
Oh, girl. She went on the uh she went on
the uh what's her name? She was so happy
to talk to her, baby. Oprah was so Oh my
god. Finally, a black that understands
me. Period.
Girl, Kiki Palmer don't care about none
of that. Kiki Palmer just like, "Girl, I
just know this going to do some views.
This gonna do numbers." That's all Kiki
Palmer be like, "Girl, this gonna do
some numbers." That watch you had
Jonathan Major on her stuff. She don't
be caring. She like, "Girl, this gonna
do some numbers." Period. one or the
other of those people and say Maya and
Sydney more so than anybody else. But
>> oh
else, but I would have to say um
>> yeah,
>> what did you need?
>> Yeah. [laughter]
>> Being on the phone with Maya Angelou
sounds all the time go wrong.
I'm
>> Kiki Palm is a She's an impersonator.
She can I mean
She's an imperson. I'm telling like
that's she impersonating MyAngelo. She
is a Whitney Houston impersonator.
I'm telling y'all like I'm not lying.
Like she's literally I wasn't expecting
this clip. Like this is this is her.
[laughter]
Kiki, you're so funny. I love it.
Um but yeah, it was it seemed like it
was a cute interview. Um Oprah went on
to talk about you know the um infamous
gift of her like oh like being shocked
and oh my gosh um and like she don't
like being surprised and stuff. It was
it seemed like it was a good interview.
I haven't watched all of it but I am
curious of Oprah Winfrey. I'm curious of
what like what is going on in her mind.
Um but I feel like this was PR for her
because Oprah don't normally talk to
regular folks. She don't talk to regular
people, but um she she did this
interview
uh and they talked about a lot of, you
know, things and I'm sure it was funny.
I don't have much to add. Um cuz I
haven't watched all of it, but
I just feel like if anything, the take
away from me, this is this is PR for
Oprah. Um, even if this interview was
planned like it it's coming at the right
time.
Justin, will you ever talk about Drag
Race? Um,
I honestly could not tell you because
I'm not watching no more Drag Race after
they played played in my girl face.
RuPaul. Rupaul.
I've talked about Drag Race and I and I
my um I had an opinion about Drag Race.
I don't think um that RuPaul is a um I
don't consider her as a black icon. Um
yeah, I just don't I don't consider
RuPaul a black icon. Um she don't like
being around black folks. So, I'm just
like she's an icon. She's a legend, but
she's not a black icon to me. Um she's
just, you know, iconic, but she's not a
black icon. There's a difference. I give
that to folks who like to be around
black folks and are
like, I'm black.
Like I I can't get into Drag Race. It's
too white. It's like I
I did not I was against watching Drag
Race because all I saw was black fans
complaining about the racism on the show
and how the black drag queens were
treated. So I was like, I'm not
watching. It's definitely not. And to
me, just looking at the show, this looks
like a white person show. Like can we be
honest? The show looks very white. I'm
not surprised. Like all the jokes and
stuff, all the culture, it's white. like
it's white. Like you can look at the the
um the the boys, they be bringing out
pit crew. The pit crew is white. None of
them men look like Calvin Klein models.
And I'm not baby. I was even sneaking
and watch looking at them type of models
when I was um 16 working at TJ Maxx.
Like it's the pit crew. I have ne the
pit crew ain't never did nothing for me.
Just the white hairy men with muscles
like I'm good. They have they they
sprinkle one knitter in there every once
in a while to let y'all know, hey, we do
they have the knitters as a dancers
though,
but it's a white show. You can look at
the show and tell it's white. So, I can
only hold my nose for so long and I have
a big nose. So, I can only hold it for
so long. So, I'm like, I I I can only
hold it for so long. But, they played in
my girl face this last season. Um, and I
said, I'm not watching no more of this.
And I and my friend was like, damn, you
really ain't watching. No, I'm not
watching no more. Sorry. Um,
period. like I I stand on business,
period. Um, are there any other final
questions before I call it a night? Oh,
shout out to the patrons. I
did a video
talking about um
blackowned restaurants and the situation
that's happening with um Toast on Linux.
Um, I did a video about that and um, I
cannot wait to put that out uh, as soon
as um, you know, I'm probably gonna drop
that. I'm gonna drop that Thursday. I'm
probably going to drop that Thursday
afternoon. Um, and I recorded my video
about
the gays. The gays. I did my video about
that. Um, and I'm going to edit that
Thursday. I'm not doing no work
tomorrow. I have to go find some shoes,
y'all. I have to go find some shoes. I'm
gonna You know what? I was not going to
show y'all a picture of this, but I want
I want to end on a funny note. If y'all
want to see something real funny, hold
on for just a second. So, I had bought
some heels. I'm working on something
very special. Very special.
I'm working on something very special.
And I ain't never wore no woman's shoe
before.
I never I ain't never wore no woman's
shoe before. So, you know, I'm thinking,
"Oh, girl, I'm just gonna get, you know,
I'm gonna get 11, a size 11." You know,
this should be, you know, you know, this
should be good. Girl, I put on these
shoes.
Let me see if I can I got to put it on
the screen. I got to put it on the
screen, child. I I It won't let me put
that shoe on there. Oh, this is messed
up. It won't let me put this shoe on
here.
It won't let me put the shoe on there.
Let me see if I can do it.
Replace
a girl. She will not let me put Oh,
girl. Am I going This is
I got to let y'all see this this heel,
child. I have got to let y'all see this.
I got to
Give me a second, y'all. Give me
[laughter]
Hold. Hold on one.
Okay, there it is. Okay, there we go.
Shoe cam. We can going to give y baby
my I tried to stuff my big toe in here,
girl. [laughter]
Girl, I got a size 11.
I was going to try to wear a little heel
for this for this for this thing. Baby,
[laughter]
I was like, how baby, I could not I had
to I had to wait on my foot. I had to
[laughter]
girl. I said I had to send her back.
Send her back.
Send them back. I If I show y'all the
other picture, y'all g y'all y'all
better not put this on YouTube. Y'all
better not You better not.
Cuz if you see the front,
if you see the front, you going to
scream. Let me see if I have the picture
of the front.
I'm trying not to reveal the outfit, but
I want y'all to see the front of the
shoe. Babe, my foot so fat. It's
ridicul. I said, "This is ridiculous.
This is ridiculous."
Like, I hate it so much.
Something is happening when on my
I guess I'll let me see. But yeah, girl.
Like my my foot was literally giving
this.
Like my foot was lit.
My foot was literally giving this.
Girl, these was not no Margela. Girl,
these was some um Steve Madden. Don't
play with me.
These were some Steve Madden, child.
They was $170. Period. Think you think
I'm going to spend $1,400 on on on one
damn shoe? Please. You got me confused
with somebody else. I ain't child.
Please. But this was my foot. My foot is
fat. Like my foot is wide. Like it was
literally leaning y'all. It was so bad.
Like this is Look at You see it coming
out. Like look at my foot. She coming
all out doing this.
Like it looks swole. It looked like my
foot had allergic reaction.
I had to take them things off like they
girls that salt retention please.
[laughter]
AOA is off.
I wanted it to work. [laughter]
Y'all whacking me a little too much. My
friend said, "Is them tabies?" I said,
"No, girl. These are fabies." Cuz my
foot is fat and they
aa
Oh yeah, these girl. If I had wore these
for my for my shoot, the girls would
have uh [laughter]
Let me block Kevin.
Let me I'm gonna block you, Kevin.
Kevin gonna say my feet look [laughter]
Is this the leprechaun?
>> [laughter]
>> Babe, my pinky toe was on fire through
the fire. Through the
This is
I'm talking about my foot was stuffed.
It's pig. It's pigs in the blanket.
I put this on. I said there's no the
moment. Let me see if I can Where the
shoe at? Hold on y'all. Give me a
second.
Y'all,
when I saw the shoe, I'm not supposed to
be showing y'all this cuz I'm supposed
to be shaking y'all up, but the people
who watching, y'all going, but I can
tell like they might not even knew. I
can tell. I said, "Oh, girl, my foot is
too fat. It's not going to fit in this."
Like I said, "Oh, girl, this is not
she's not gonna work for me."
Like,
[laughter]
like this is not
my foot. It's not my shoe. My foot can
get in it, but my It's stretching it out
like this is going to turn into a
Chipotle burrito.
I can't I can't do it.
I can't do it. I cannot It's not going
to work.
It's [laughter]
>> [clears throat]
>> I cannot. Y'all ain't gonna be
my women. So they say women's feet are
narrow. Is that true? Are y'all feet
narrow? Like y'all shoes are narrow.
Like there I'm hearing that you know
when it come to y'all like y'all all
y'all feet ain't created equal.
There's some women with some fat feet.
Baby, as soon as soon I open I said
these ain't gonna fit. But I said, "Let
me see if I can squeeze my tiny neck."
But my Yeah, my feet are [laughter]
Hey, buckaroo.
Girl, Kelly ate that up. Hey, buckaroo.
I scream when she said that. Hey,
buckaroo.
I'm screaming. Uh, they had w They
didn't. And the size 12 Steve Matt
didn't even have them in stock. But let
me tell you something. If I had got the
the Mian whatever Margello, the
marshmallow shoes, whatever Marshall,
whatever the hell they call, it's too
rich for my blood. I would have pulled a
charade with field. I would have wor
them things and took them right back. We
would put some tape on the bottom of it.
I would have took them right back. Right
back.
$1,200 for a shoe, child. Please. for
one shoe.
Girl, that shoe better be signed by
Martin Luther King in his march. Okay,
I'm not $1,200. What? Who? 1200 $1,400
for
child, please. Um, but I'm I I got to go
tomorrow and find some shoes for um
something I'm working on. Um, so I I'mma
be on the hunt tomorrow, y'all. So, if
y'all see me out, I'm on the hunt. I'mma
be in the women's section looking for
some heels. Um, not that so Raven when
she swelled up. See, I'm gonna get off.
I'm f to get off. You going to ban me
banned. All right, y'all. I appreciate
y'all for joining me for the live. I
will talk to y'all to Well, not
tomorrow. Thursday
later. Make sure I hit the right
buttons. Okay, there we go. Good night,
big ones. I'll talk.
>> Good night, big one. Okay, I knew it was
the reason I